[microphone feedback]
[♪ opening theme music playing]
FLEX X COP 2
CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
ALL CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
FILMED IN A SAFE ENVIRONMENT
We got a report of a body. Rosebud Hotel.
PREVIOUSLY
It looks like she's been dead for a while.
[Dr. Yoon] It's been at least 12 hours.
She was stabbed in three places,
but there's not much bleeding.
Do you know the victim?
Her name's Oh Minyeong. She's a concierge.
Men just wouldn't leave her alone.
She's gorgeous.
Have you seen anyone suspicious lately?
Ah! Room 701.
There's a suspect
in the seventh-floor suite.
[housekeeper] I heard he's a chaebol heir.
He kept calling for Minyeong,
saying he had requests to make.
-Chunsik?
-Isoo!
You've been here three weeks.
-Did you run away from home?
-No, I just...
Is it because of Ms. Oh Minyeong?
[Chunsik] The person
I fell for at first sight is...
It's you, Minyeong.
Minyeong.
I'm sorry. I have a boyfriend.
Minyeong...
Do you know anyone who might've had
a grudge against Ms. Oh Minyeong?
[Seran] I saw everything, you bitch!
You've got it all wrong. It's not me!
You psycho bitch!
Do you have any idea
who you're dealing with? Huh?
-Who was she?
-It was the hotel owner's wife.
The owner was dating Ms. Oh Minyeong?
There were rumors
that he was in love with her.
I have nothing else to say.
I said we're not done.
Let go.
[soft thud]
He tried to drag her into Room 709?
That room has been vacant for two months.
I kept that room for my own personal use.
We took the carpet in for testing,
and there wasn't enough blood.
I don't think she was murdered here.
She died somewhere else?
[♪ foreboding music playing]
What's this?
[sniffs]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
Are you checking out?
[♪ music fades]
[Ms. Delta] Detective Jin, it's Room 701.
I came in to clean,
and I found something
that looks like blood.
What?
[♪ tense suspenseful music playing]
Kang Chunsik.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[swears softly]
[engine roaring, tires screech]
[Hyera exclaims] Watch out!
Don't worry. My car's more expensive.
[scoffs] How dare he try to take me on?
[grunts softly]
[♪ upbeat rock music playing]
-[siren blaring]
-[Isoo exclaims smugly]
[tires screech, engine revs]
[engine roaring]
Hey, hey.
Vehicle ahead, stop the car.
The trust-fund kid in car 6383!
Stop the car!
What's he doing?
[groans anxiously]
[Isoo, over loudspeaker] Stop the car!
[tires screeching]
[siren continues blaring]
My good citizens!
Chunsik Food's sole heir is on the run!
We are police.
Kang Chunsik is on the run!
Kang Chunsik, stop the damn car!
[sighs defeatedly]
[tires screeching]
[♪ tense, gripping music playing]
That brat just won't listen.
Here we go.
-[engine revs]
-[tires screeching]
[tires screech]
[tires screeching]
[siren continues blaring]
[seat belt unbuckles]
[Hyera sighs]
[siren stops]
-What the hell are you doing?
-Mr. Kang Chunsik.
You're under arrest
for the murder of Oh Minyeong.
-[handcuffs clicking]
-What?
Isoo. Why are you doing this to me?
What do you mean?
You just ran from the police.
We're taking you into custody, punk.
[sputters]
[snarls]
[Chunsik sputters]
Isoo!
[♪ tense pulsating music playing]
EPISODE 6
[♪ music increases in tempo]
What kind of steak knife
comes with room service?
[♪ music fades]
Why did you run away?
I was just on my way home.
My car's just really fast.
You said Ms. Oh Minyeong
left your room around 7:40 p.m.
That's right.
What did you do after that?
Oh, for god's sake.
Answer the question.
I was drinking because I was upset.
[♪ tense, foreboding music playing]
[sniffles]
[crying softly]
[sniffles, sobbing]
And then?
[Chunsik] I ran out of alcohol,
so I went to the bar.
[sniffles]
Evening, sir.
-The usual, please.
-Yes, sir.
I was there until around 10:00 p.m.
-[sighs softly]
-[cell phone vibrating]
DETECTIVE PARK JUNYOUNG
[Junyoung] The photo below is
Rosebud Restaurant's steak knife.
Were you angry Ms. Oh rejected you?
Of course I was.
So you called her back, didn't you?
[♪ ominous music playing]
-You stabbed her with the steak knife.
-What?
Minyeong.
Please don't kill me.
[flesh squelches]
[flesh squelching]
[blood splatters]
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
What on earth are you talking about?
[Hyera] Here.
-This is Room 701, where you stayed.
-That's right.
-We found blood there.
-[gasps softly]
[♪ tense, ticking music playing]
And signs that the floor had been cleaned.
Where is the knife?
Wait...
You mean...
Minyeong...
died in my hotel room?
That's exactly what we're saying.
But I... [gags]
I slept there.
[thud]
Seriously, why is he always passing out?
[both sigh]
[knock at door]
-[officer] Did you call?
-[Hyera] Yes.
Please lock him up when he's awake.
Is he okay?
He's fine. He'll wake up
if you give him some water.
[♪ tense, gripping music playing]
Hello.
I'm with the police.
Right.
By any chance,
do you remember this guest?
Ah...
I do.
Did he come here on the night of the 13th?
Yes.
I was supposed to get off at 8:00 p.m.,
but the night staff didn't show,
so I was stuck on duty.
I had plans, but I couldn't make it.
What time was that?
It was a little before 8:30 p.m.
Around 8:20.
KEY SUSPECTS
KANG CHUNSIK
YEOM JAESEOP, CHA SERAN, YEOM KIJOO
I really don't think it's Chunsik.
[cell phone vibrating]
Hello?
He came to the bar around 8:20 p.m.
Got it.
-[line disconnects]
-Pull up the bar hallway.
[mouse clicking]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[keyboard key clacks]
[sighs softly]
Oh, there he is.
[sighs] It doesn't look like
Chunsik's our guy.
He may not look like it,
but he's a good kid.
He killed the victim in a fit of rage,
went up to the bar for a drink,
returned to get rid of the body,
and wiped the floor.
Kang Chunsik is the only one
who can do that.
Then how did he move the body?
Did he carry her?
And even if he knew about
Room 709 through the rumors,
how would he get in?
He doesn't have a key.
He could've called someone to do it.
[sighs] Without the camera,
we can't confirm anything.
Did you check all the footage?
No, not even half.
There's too much to go through.
-Let's split it. Send it over.
-Yes, ma'am.
Time of death was around 8:00 to 9:00 p.m.
We have to find everyone
who entered the hotel, took the elevator,
or got off on the seventh floor
during that time.
Understood.
SEOUL GANGHA POLICE STATION
DETECTIVE DIVISION
[keyboard key clacks]
[mouse clicks]
Aren't you guys hungry?
Let's order some food.
I'll order it. How about a sandwich?
Sounds good. I'll get a beef sandwich.
Beef.
[♪ quirky music playing]
Detective Joo?
I'll get the Italian B.M.T.
Ooh.
Italian B.M.T.
This is yours, bro.
-This is Detective Joo's.
-[in English] Thank you.
Beef sandwich is the way to go.
It's stuffed with meat.
[in Korean] You need ham in a sandwich.
[sighs] We never see eye to eye.
They're both delicious.
[Taegyun] Detective Joo!
-What...
-Yes?
[♪ music fades]
You're all...
Can I have a word?
Yes, sir.
What was that?
-Did you arrest the heir of Chunsik Food?
-Yes.
Is he definitely guilty?
He's our prime suspect so far.
He also fled, so we arrested him.
What if he's innocent? Huh?
Are you going to make me look bad?
Do the reporters know?
What will you do if he's not the culprit?
Sir.
Why are you so worried?
If it's not him, I'll handle it.
I'm friends with his dad. We're mutuals.
[♪ jaunty music playing]
[sighs] In any case, just get it right!
Get it right!
Gosh,
how did someone so timid
become a police chief, huh?
[sighs softly]
[chuckles softly]
[scoffs softly]
[♪ music fades]
SEWON HOSPITAL
KANG JINKYUNG
HEMATOLOGIST-ONCOLOGIST
[mouse clicks]
[knock at door]
Yes, come in.
[door closes]
Mr. Choi Jeonghun?
Please have a seat.
[sighs]
I've gone over your test results,
and there's a malignant tumor
in your stomach.
[♪ gentle melancholy music playing]
Uh, right.
Don't worry too much. We can treat it.
Uh, the tumor isn't that large,
but I think surgery will be necessary.
-Uh...
-Please don't overthink it.
It's just like a car accident
that could happen to anyone.
I'll help you get better.
-[chuckles softly]
-[♪ music fades]
[clicks tongue]
[exhales shakily]
[cell phone vibrating]
DETECTIVE JIN ISOO
-Hello?
-[Isoo] Mr. Choi.
Did you go to the hospital?
Yes, I'm there now.
-Did you get checked out?
-Yes. They said everything's fine.
[sighs in relief] That's a relief.
I was scared that you were seriously ill.
What's there to be scared about?
You're the only family I have now.
Don't get sick, okay?
Eat only the good stuff. No whiskey.
[♪ gentle melancholy music playing]
All right.
You promised,
so it's your turn to see a psychiatrist.
Okay, fine.
I'll go after catching the killer.
Gotta go.
All right.
[clicks tongue]
[sighs wearily]
[♪ music swells, fades]
SEOUL GANGHA POLICE STATION
The forensic results are here.
The one who asked Yeom Jaeseop
to meet in Room 709 was Ms. Oh Minyeong.
They spoke several times.
Yeom transferred
100 million won to her twice.
[♪ tense suspenseful music playing]
[Minyeong] Come to Room 709.
These texts sound a little strange.
Where is Yeom Jaeseop right now?
Kyungjin is tracking him.
Yeom Jaeseop left the country!
Where did he go?
[panting] Hanoi. He just got on board.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
If he disappears, we can't find him.
Contact Hanoi Airport and
get immigration...
[♪ music fades]
Oh.
You have a private jet.
How did you know about that?
I saw it on the news.
-Can you catch up with him?
-[in English] Of course!
[in Korean] Let's go!
[♪ upbeat swing jazz music playing]
[engine roaring]
[tires screech]
Come on, run!
Captain!
We're off to Hanoi!
We have to catch the killer! Hey!
Run!
[Kyungjin] Detective Joo!
Awesome photo, right?
[Hyera] Am I the only one embarrassed?
[Isoo] Just accept it!
[Kyungjin] Ta-da!
The Hansu private jet.
This is the premium bar.
It has all kinds of drinks
and even a fridge. And a kettle, too.
Oh, this chair. It's really comfortable.
Try sitting down.
[♪ quirky music playing]
-[both sigh contentedly]
-It's nice.
When do you use this?
Hmm... Whenever.
When I go scuba diving or throw parties.
Ah, I also ride it on December 31st
and follow the setting sun.
Classic rich-people behavior.
It must be nice being rich.
It definitely doesn't hurt.
Hey,
how much does this cost?
This?
-What?
-Makes you jealous, right?
I'll lend it to you when you propose.
-Really?
-Yes.
I love you, bro.
-[chuckles]
-[Isoo] Mmm. Yeah, me too.
You promised.
-Promise.
-Okay, for god's sake.
You all heard, right? [chuckles]
Hey.
Would you lend it to me, too?
You want to get married?
Are you going to propose?
No, I mean,
if the time comes.
You thought that far ahead?
Isn't it a little too soon?
[clears throat] Hey, I'll make a great MC.
[clears throat] We will
now begin the wedding
of Groom Park Junyoung
and Bride Yoon Jiwon.
-Please welcome...
-Our groom!
Oh?
I'm going to the restroom.
[vocalizing the "Wedding March"]
The restroom's up front.
Stupid.
[♪ music fades]
[♪ suspenseful, foreboding music playing]
[♪ music swells, fades]
[flight attendant, over PA]
Ladies and gentlemen,
we have arrived
at Noi Bai International Airport.
VIETNAM
HANOI AIRPORT
[siren blaring]
[Isoo, in English, over megaphone]
Ladies and gentlemen!
This is Jin Isoo Air!
[in Korean] We are urgently looking
for Mr. Yeom Jaeseop!
[♪ upbeat swing jazz music playing]
I repeat,
we are urgently looking
for Mr. Yeom Jaeseop!
Would Mr. Yeom Jaeseop
please have his passport ready
and transfer to this aircraft.
Jin Isoo is here!
Mr. Yeom Jaeseop!
[♪ music fades]
SEOUL GANGHA POLICE STATION
[♪ tense, ticking music playing]
You met Ms. Oh Minyeong at 7:50 p.m.
on the day of the murder.
Just come clean.
We've already checked everything.
[sighs softly]
Why did you meet her?
Because of my wife.
I needed to talk to her.
What did you talk about?
She was angry after your wife grabbed
her by the hair, right?
Yes.
So I tried to make it up to her.
I'm sorry.
Whatever.
When the new hotel opens up,
I'll make you a manager there.
-Really?
-Of course.
Oh, you.
-[doorbell rings]
-[Seran] Jaeseop!
[banging on door]
-Are you in there?
-[doorbell rings]
[♪ tense, gripping music playing]
[whispering] I'll go first,
so you can come out later.
I didn't see her after that.
What time was that?
[sighs softly]
I think it was around 8:00 p.m.
What did you do before going back
to your office at 8:20 p.m.?
I was on the phone, at the stairwell.
At the stairwell? With whom?
It was a business call.
OH MINYEONG BANK STATEMENT
You gave Ms. Oh 200 million won.
100 million two months ago,
and another 100 million last week.
It was a form of compensation.
Because my wife hit her.
Oh, he must be really well-off.
Two hundred million won.
[sighs]
Are you going to keep lying?
She blackmailed you, didn't she?
[♪ gripping suspenseful music playing]
[Minyeong] When are you
going to send me the money?
If you keep this up,
you're going to regret it.
"Do not test my patience."
[sighs defeatedly, clicks tongue]
[Hyera] What's the reason?
Why did she blackmail you?
That has nothing to do with this case.
That's for us to decide.
You'd had enough of the blackmail,
so you killed her.
That's not true.
She was definitely alive
when I left the room.
If she were killed in that room,
it means someone was trying to frame me.
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
Open your eyes.
Open your eyes wide.
Mmm. [in English] Okay.
"Leo"?
[in Korean] Who's Leo?
Leonardo DiCa... Him?
[♪ gripping suspenseful music playing]
ROSEBUD HOTEL STAFF ROSTER
FRONT DESK JEON YUJIN
EMPLOYEE RECORD
It's him. Jeon Yujin.
NAME JEON YUJIN
Right, Mr. Jeon Yujin.
He was the one in the CEO's office.
-Check the camera outside the office.
-[Kyungjin] Okay.
[keyboard clacking]
[mouse clicking]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[keyboard keys clacking]
-[keyboard key clacks]
-[Kyungjin] That's a bit strange.
[keyboard key clacks]
What employee barges
into the CEO's office?
We have a new suspect.
The CEO's mistress.
No, his male lover.
[♪ music swells, stops]
Mr. Yeom.
The one you love is Jeon Yujin, isn't it?
[sighs defeatedly]
I didn't know I'd turn out this way.
I'm married, and I even have a kid.
[♪ soft, enthralling music playing]
I fell for him like crazy.
TWO MONTHS EARLIER
-Sir.
-Yes, Mr. Yu.
-These are our new employees.
-Ah.
Nice to meet you.
Welcome to our hotel.
-[employee 1] Cheers.
-[employee 2] Cheers.
[♪ gentle music playing]
[meat sizzling]
-Let me pour you one.
-Thank you.
[Yujin] I look forward
to working with you.
Enjoy your food.
Sir, let me pour you a glass, too.
[employee 3] Thank you.
Thank you for dinner.
Have a safe trip home.
Take care.
Sir...
Watch your step.
Thank you.
[♪ music turns suspenseful]
Stop the car.
[car honks]
Get in. I'll take you home.
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
Dry yourself.
[♪ gentle music playing]
Don't start anything if you're not sure.
I don't want to get hurt anymore.
Yujin.
Even if you're an alien,
or a man...
I really don't know anymore. [sighs]
Let's see this through to the end.
[♪ music fades]
[inhales sharply]
We met secretly in Room 709.
[glasses clink]
[♪ gripping suspenseful music playing]
Mmm. It's good.
Yes, it's delicious.
Do you like wine?
Oh, I do.
[Jaeseop] It felt like a dream.
But...
it didn't last long.
[door closes]
[Jaeseop] Then the blackmail started.
[scoffs] Mr. Yeom.
Why are you so cheap?
You really think this is enough?
[♪ tense pulsating music playing]
[sighs wearily]
So I sent her 100 million won.
Then my wife caused a scene,
so I sent her another 100 million.
But that day,
she said she wanted to see me.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[sighs wearily]
Minyeong, what do you want me to do?
[sighs] My feet are killing me.
[sighs wearily]
I think I might quit.
I don't want to come into work,
and I'm sick of all the annoying guests.
Mr. Yeom.
I'd like a leaving bonus.
I don't have any money.
If you don't have money,
what does that make me?
[doorbell rings]
[Seran] Honey! Get out here!
[Seran] Are you in there?
Where are you?
Look who's busted.
[Seran] Come out here!
Shall I open the door?
[Jaeseop] Wait.
Okay, fine.
I want one billion won.
I need time.
Will a month do?
Mr. Yeom, I'm going
to take leave starting tomorrow.
[♪ gripping, foreboding music playing]
[Jaeseop sighs wearily]
[line connects, ringing]
Yujin. [sighs wearily]
Let's end this.
What's wrong?
Did Oh Minyeong blackmail you again?
There's nothing more to say. Let's end it.
I told you not to start if you're unsure.
You said you'd see it through.
This is the end! Don't you get it?
Then what am I supposed to do?
How can I work here
when I have to see you?
Then you leave! You can just quit!
Jaeseop.
[door closes]
[door slams]
[sighs regretfully]
Then why did you flee?
When I heard Oh Minyeong had died,
I had a bad feeling.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Had Yujin killed her?
No, it couldn't be.
But when I heard she died in Room 709,
I thought Yujin had killed her
in that room
to get revenge on me.
I didn't know what to do,
so I just ran away.
Is this something
you can just run away from?
[♪ music fades]
By the way,
why is it "Leo"?
It's Yujin's zodiac sign.
Ah.
His zodiac sign.
Right, you're quite the romantic.
-Ah.
-[inhales softly]
-[exhales deeply]
-[Isoo] His zodiac sign.
How did it go?
It was a tragic love story.
It touched my heart. Ah.
Let's look into Jeon Yujin.
Kyungjin, trace his movements on that day.
-And find out where he is now.
-Got it.
[handcuffs clinking]
[handcuffs click open]
-[officer] Take out all your belongings.
-[handcuffs jingle]
[Chunsik] Mr. Yeom.
Did you...
kill Minyeong?
[♪ quirky dramatic music playing]
It was you, asshole.
You killed her, didn't you?
Come here.
[clanging]
[yelling] Come here right now!
[sobbing] Do you have
any idea how much I loved her?
Kang Chunsik! Get back.
What are you going to do about Minyeong?
What are you going to do about me?
[sobbing]
[♪ music fades]
[Isoo sighs softly]
-[keyboard key clacks]
-Jeon Yujin answered the call at 8:05 p.m.
Hello?
[Jaeseop] Yujin. [sighs wearily]
Let's end this.
[♪ gripping, foreboding music playing]
[Kyungjin] He left the CEO's office
and went to the bar.
[tremulous exhale]
He must've seen Chunsik there.
He would've thought of using Room 701.
Because it was well-known
that Kang Chunsik liked Ms. Oh.
I found the last footage of Ms. Oh.
I think she was on the roof.
She got on the staff elevator at 8:40 p.m.
She must have hidden out
on the roof to avoid Mr. Yeom's wife.
Fifteen minutes.
Where was Jeon Yujin during this time?
[mouse clicks]
Back to the changing room.
He must've gone to get
his radio and the master key.
This was when he decided to kill her.
[card reader beeps]
[Isoo] He snuck into Room 701.
Ms. Oh.
A call came in from Room 701.
[Isoo] He told her
Chunsik had called for her.
[♪ music swells, fades]
[sighs deeply] All we have is the motive.
No murder weapon,
and the radio call
wouldn't have been logged.
Where's Jeon Yujin after that?
[keyboard keys clacking]
The elevator.
[♪ tense suspenseful music playing]
There's only an eight-minute gap.
In that time, he killed the victim,
moved the body, and cleaned up?
That's impossible, isn't it?
-It's impossible, without an accomplice.
-No, wait.
Why move the body?
He saw Chunsik at the bar
and called her to Room 701
to dump it on Chunsik.
[♪ pensive music playing]
That's true.
There's no reason to move the body.
What if after killing her,
he wanted to get revenge
on Yeom Jaeseop and moved the body?
No, that can't be done in eight minutes.
[inhales sharply]
This wasn't a premeditated murder.
How can there be an accomplice?
What on earth could have happened?
Who moved the body and even cleaned up?
Someone who knows
that the security camera was broken.
Someone who can move
without drawing attention
and move the body
without raising any suspicion.
Someone who has access to all the rooms.
Someone who can clean perfectly.
-Housekeeping.
-[gasps] No way.
What about housekeeping?
Yeom could've given the order
after finding out Jeon had killed her.
[♪ ominous music playing]
[breath trembling] I killed her.
I...
I ended up killing her.
I'll take care of it.
Get out of there right now.
In the room he personally used?
He probably hid the body first
to deal with later.
We'll go to the hotel,
so identify the housekeeping staff.
And find out where Jeon dumped his jacket.
-[Kyungjin] Understood.
-Okay.
[♪ tense pulsating music playing]
How could it be one of those ladies?
-It's so good.
-It's really delicious.
Now I see why it's 100,000 won.
Is there anyone you can rule out?
There is.
Gosh, you keep calling us ladies
and flattering us like that.
[sighs] If that was an act,
she deserves an Oscar.
[♪ music fades]
[Isoo scoffs]
There you are.
What? What is it?
Did you find the killer?
Uh, well...
-We have something to ask you.
-What is it?
Were any of the housekeeping staff
acting suspiciously on the day
of the murder or the next day?
What? Us, the housekeeping staff?
What are you talking about?
Someone moved Ms. Oh Minyeong's body.
[stutters] Someone
from the housekeeping staff?
Who?
It's a possibility.
Did anyone seem odd?
Oh... [mutters]
[gasps]
What is it?
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
She was cleaning the cart.
She said she spilled coffee on it.
My gosh.
-[chuckles nervously]
-What are you doing?
I spilled some coffee.
-Really?
-Yes.
You startled me.
You should clock out.
I'll tidy up in here.
-Okay.
-Bye.
We found her. It's Na Yeonhong.
[♪ gripping, foreboding music playing]
EMPLOYEE RECORD
NA YEONHONG
SON: JEON YUJIN
She's Jeon Yujin's mom.
[line disconnects]
She knew her son killed someone
and covered it up.
-[door opens]
-[sighs softly]
[♪ music swells, stabilizes]
[♪ pulsating foreboding music playing]
[doorbell rings]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music stabilizes]
[breathes tremulously]
[gasps]
[gasping]
[breathing frantically]
[♪ tense pulsating music playing]
[crying]
[exclaims]
[sobbing]
[hyperventilating]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[catches breath]
[grunts, exclaims]
[breathing frantically]
MINYEONG
-[continues breathing frantically]
-[bottle spraying]
We'll find evidence if we check the cart.
Let's arrest Ms. Na Yeonhong first.
Wait.
Let me talk to her first.
[♪ gentle melancholy music playing]
[♪ music fades]
Something on your mind?
No, nothing. [chuckles softly]
Would you like some tea?
Thank you.
Here.
[exhales softly]
[♪ soft tense music playing]
One moment, please.
[♪ soft, pensive music playing]
[inhales sharply] You must be tired.
I'm fine. [chuckles]
Everyone has to make a living.
My mom
died when I was young.
Gosh, I'm sorry to hear that.
I was lonely, so I acted out
and did a lot of stupid things.
[chuckles softly]
No matter how badly I messed up,
she'd be on my side, right?
Of course.
To a mother,
her child will always be her baby.
There's nothing
she wouldn't do for her child. [chuckles]
You're right.
My mom would've been the same.
But if I...
committed an unforgivable crime,
and if my mom was punished
for trying to protect me,
I would probably...
never be able to forgive myself.
Please tell me
what happened.
[♪ soft, suspenseful music playing]
I killed her.
This isn't the right thing for Yujin.
Please reconsider.
[crying] I'm sorry.
[♪ music fades]
Please tell the truth.
Everything will come to light in the end.
[♪ gentle, somber music playing]
[sniffles]
I killed Ms. Oh Minyeong.
Get up.
Ms. Na Yeonhong,
you're under arrest
for Ms. Oh Minyeong's murder.
-[handcuffs rattle, click]
-You have the right to an attorney
and the right to remain silent.
You won't be penalized
for remaining silent.
[gasps]
Stop right there!
[sobbing]
[exclaims]
[Yujin] Wait!
[gasping] No, Yujin!
-I killed her.
-[sobbing] Yujin!
No.
Yujin...
My mom did nothing wrong.
[Yeonhong] No, Yujin, no.
Yujin, my baby.
[continues sobbing] Yujin, no.
Yujin!
No, not you.
-No, Yujin.
-I'm sorry.
My baby.
I was the one who killed her.
[yelling] Me!
Oh, my goodness.
Please, no, my baby.
My baby.
[♪ melancholy music playing]
-[sniffles]
-[continues sobbing]
[Yujin] You're right.
I called her over to Room 701
and killed her.
[slow footsteps approaching]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[door closes]
[sighs]
What are you doing?
Just stop.
[scoffs]
Stop what?
You got your money.
So stop blackmailing us.
I basically struck gold here.
Would you stop if you were me?
[sighs in exasperation]
[breathes shakily]
You...
Are you out of your mind?
Yes, I'm out of my mind.
[flesh squelching]
[♪ tense, ominous music playing]
[blood splatters]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[breath trembling]
[♪ music fades]
Then I heard the body was found
in Room 709,
so I thought
Mr. Yeom had covered up for me.
[♪ gentle melancholy music playing]
[crying] I had no idea it was my mom.
I guess you didn't tell the hotel
you were working with your mother.
No.
She's been working there for a while,
and I...
I started working this year.
My mom said we should act like strangers,
because nothing good would come from it.
[sobbing] After she got divorced,
I was all she had.
Because of me...
my mom...
All you're worried about is your mom
after you murdered someone?
You're a murderer.
You ended someone's life.
[sniffles, sobbing]
Was it worth all that?
[♪ music fades]
[pen scratching]
Mr. Yeom Jaeseop, Mr. Kang Chunsik,
you're cleared of all suspicion.
You are free to go.
-Jaeseop!
-Dad!
[exhales sharply] What happened, huh?
Did you kill her?
No.
Then what?
You're cheating, aren't you?
It's all over. Just stop.
[exhales deeply]
You're a coward until the end.
Why did you even start it?
[sighs regretfully]
It's Leo.
Seran.
Yujin is the one I love.
[♪ quirky music playing]
Yujin?
Wait,
who the hell is Yujin?
Oh, my god.
[gasps softly]
Then why did Minyeong die?
She was a blackmailer.
She blackmailed them and was murdered.
My sweet, angelic Minyeong
was a blackmailer?
Don't pass out, seriously.
Huh?
-[thud]
-[both exclaim]
Kang Chunsik!
[breathing heavily] Now even a man is...
A man... [exclaims]
Come on, seriously?
Is passing out contagious now?
What the heck?
For god's sake!
Hello, 119?
Yes, this is Gangha Police Station.
[sighs contentedly]
[sighs in relief]
Let's go drink some soju, team.
Yes, sir.
-We should go for a beer, too.
-Sounds great.
I have plans, so I'll get going.
Stay for one drink. We caught the killer.
I'm already late. I'm off.
-Okay, bye.
-See you tomorrow.
Have a good evening!
What kind of team leader
skips drinks with the team?
Come on, bro. Let's go.
My feelings are hurt.
-Seriously, I'm hurt.
-[Junyoung] Let's go.
She got a boyfriend? What's with her?
-[Isoo] Cheers!
-[Kyungjin] Cheers!
[exhales sharply]
[Kyungjin and Isoo exhale sharply]
Mmm!
Hey, this flavor is insane.
I've been craving this lately.
They're famous for their gopdoritang,
but this is good too, right?
It's so sweet and savory.
[Junyoung] I can't stop eating it.
I'll have to come back next time.
With who? Your girlfriend?
No.
By myself.
I saw they have meals for one here.
I'm coming back for lunch by myself.
Mmm...
[♪ jaunty music playing]
[sighs deeply]
This case was driven by
an all-consuming love.
Love is all-consuming by nature.
Is it?
Is it, Junyoung?
[sighs] I've never had
an office romance before.
It's fun to secretly date
a coworker, right?
How does it feel? Tell me, I'm curious.
That's enough.
I don't know who it is.
I just had a feeling
you were dating a coworker.
Yeah, who could it be? I'm dying to know.
Ah!
No wonder he always
volunteered to go to the morgue.
I noticed a long time ago.
I've been dating since I was
in seventh grade.
I'm a dating expert.
Will you two just shut up?
I don't think so. I'm going to say more.
You should be keeping things professional.
The autopsy room? How dare you!
The autopsy room, what?
-It's where your love blossomed.
-The autopsy room!
[Dr. Yoon] You guys are awful.
[Junyoung] Jiwon.
Yes, we're dating.
Is that really something
to tease him about?
-What's with you two?
-No.
We should celebrate. Right, Kyungjin?
Yes, of course.
Right.
[Isoo] Here, let me pour you one.
[Dr. Yoon clears throat]
I thought you were the Grim Reaper.
Leave my Junyoung alone.
You know what my job is, right?
-Congratulations.
-Congratulations from me, too!
-Cheers.
[♪ music fades]
That hits the spot.
How did you two end up together?
Well, we just
met by chance
and ended up eating together.
That wasn't by chance.
What?
[♪ upbeat quirky music playing]
I timed it and waited for you.
Waited!
Uh...
Really? I had no idea.
-Dummy.
-[sighs wearily]
Even a guy that clueless has a girlfriend.
I know.
[sighs] I don't get it at all. Cheers.
[glasses clink]
Remember, I asked you where you lived.
[Isoo gags]
[glasses clink]
-[meat sizzling]
-[exhales]
[exhales sharply]
Uh, you look well.
That's freelancing for you.
It's great not being a cop.
All those reports.
Just thinking about it ruins my drink.
[both laugh]
What about you?
What's it like being back at Gangha?
I like it.
There's a real thrill
in catching murderers one by one.
[sighs deeply] I kind of miss that.
What's Jin Isoo like?
Jin Isoo is
resourceful and quick on his feet.
[chuckles softly]
It's fun working with him.
Ah...
I thought you'd be missing me.
Uh, you're the one who decided to leave.
-[chuckles]
-Here.
-Cheers.
-[glasses clink]
[sighs softly]
He's coming back in two days.
[♪ tense suspenseful music playing]
I've got everything ready.
[♪ music fades]
Sometimes, I suddenly can't breathe.
For no reason at all,
I feel like the walls are closing in
when I'm inside places like elevators.
I want to hear your story first.
What kind of story?
Let's start with your parents.
Your brother, the one you trusted
the most, killed your parents.
[♪ soft, poignant music playing]
I'd like to hear how you feel about that.
Did you know that I caught a psychiatrist?
She hypnotized me and even killed people.
That's why I'm not a big fan
of psychiatrists.
I'd rather you just give me
the medication,
instead of wasting time.
[sighs softly]
You experienced
some traumatic events in the past
and also became
the target of bombings recently.
This is likely why
you are experiencing these symptoms.
Talking honestly about your feelings
and finding closure
can really help your recovery.
You think talking about it
is enough to give me closure?
Let's give it a try.
[scoffs softly]
I'll have to find another hospital.
I'll give you the medication.
Whenever you feel like talking,
we can talk then.
[♪ music fades]
[sighs softly]
[bottle clicks on table]
[♪ gripping suspenseful music playing]
ECSTASY
A BREATHLESS FALL
CLIMAX
LIGHT SCATTERED ACROSS THE UNIVERSE
DISSOLUTION
THE SILENCE OF WHISPERING REEDS
YU SEONGWON, THE SCULPTOR
WHO CAPTIVATED THE EUROPEAN ART WORLD,
RETURNS AFTER 4 YEARS
TO HOLD A SOLO EXHIBITION IN KOREA
RETURN
YU SEONGWON'S SOLO EXHIBITION
[♪ music fades]
[♪ ominous music playing]
DISSOLUTION
THE SILENCE OF WHISPERING REEDS
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
FLEX X COP 2
EPISODE 6
AS THE MYSTERY DEEPENS,
YU SEONGWON EMERGES
[♪ upbeat pop music playing]
Special Cast.
Choi Dukmoon, Lee Suk
♪ Every move was never mine ♪
♪ I don't take the checkmate ♪
[vocalizing]
[Kyungjin] Park Jaeha's magic show!
These tickets are impossible to get.
-[screaming]
-[Hyera] He died in a fire mid-show.
The escape routine went as planned.
Something did feel off, though.
-A premonition?
-Yes.
This was murder, not an accident.
Someone poured kerosene inside the coffin.
[Hyera] Who made the coffin?
Mr. Park Jaeha?
-I'm Park Jaehyung.
-[man] Twins?
Who could do something so horrific?
[gasps, yelps]
Please don't touch.
[Hyera] It was three days earlier.
[Isoo] How are a gangster
and a magician linked?
Bring that bastard in.
-[Isoo exclaims]
-Let go. Did you kill him?
[suspect] If I did,
you wouldn't even find a body.
He knew he was going to die?
Betting against me takes that much.
[♪ music fades]
[Changun] Joo Hyera.
[sighs softly]
Got a lot on your mind?
Still chasing Yu Seongwon?
YU SEONGWON RETURNS AFTER 4 YEARS
TO HOLD A SOLO EXHIBITION IN KOREA
That's why you came back, isn't it?
[♪ soft, pensive music playing]
I get how you feel.
It's a case you can never forget.
But we already
verified Yu Seongwon's alibi.
You're obsessed.
Huh?
That's what ruins a detective.
It's not an obsession.
Yu Seongwon...
will kill again.
And I'm going to stop him.
Translated by Hyesoo Lee